PERSONAL PROFILE



Open-minded student with a very positive attitude. Currently finishing his studies doing double degree program: economic analysis in University of Technology in Gdansk, Poland and Global Business Engineering in VIA University College in Horsens, Denmark. After these two experiences I would like to start my professional career improving myself in business analysis, programming, creating web sites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, testing or web engineering with ASP.NET and C#. From summer 2017 I would like to work within one of these areas and by the same time in October 2017 start part-time IT studies to improve my IT skills.

SKILLS

Jakub Lemka

JAVA C# UML HTML CSS ASP.NET JAVA SCRIPT

POSTGRE BOOTSTRAP EXCEL DESIGN SQL SQL PATTERNS

STATISTICA GRETL ADOBE GIMP VISUAL SCRUM

E-mail:

lemka.jakub@gmail.com

Phone No.:

+48 508 176 855

Date of birth:

27.11.1995

Address:

Marszalka Focha 29 81-403 Gdynia

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/jak ub-lemka **TEAMWORK**

COORDINATOR

EXPERIENCE

STRONG ORGANIZATIONAL SKILLS

EDCI II TI IDAI

INTERCULTURAL KNOWLEDGE

ADAPTABILITY

GOOD COMMUNICATION SKILLS

EDUCATION

08/2016 - now

VIA University College, Horsens, Denmark

Global Business Engineering

Bachelor degree, double diploma program Courses just from ICT department Average grade from both semesters: 4.9

10/2014 - now

Gdansk University of Technology, Poland

Economic Analysis (specialization: IT analyst)

Scholarship for the best students 2015/16, average grade: 4.62 Nomination for the best IT project in the department in 2016 Nomination for the best IT project in the department in 2017

E-mail:

lemka.jakub@gmail.com

Phone No.:

+48 508176855

Date of birth:

27.11.1995

Address:

Marszalka Focha 29 81-403 Gdynia

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/jak ub-lemka

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/2016 - 03/2016

Business consulting

Profit Plus

Place: Gdynia

Recruitment of the candidates, building a database of the clients, operations in the accounting system Taxxo, preparation

of the contracts of companies

03/2013 - now

Model

AS Management

Place: Warsaw, Paris, Seoul, Beijing

Paris Fashion Week castings, contracts in Asia – 2 months in South Korea and 3 months in China, Virgin Mobile campaign in Poland, 6-months cooperation with Polish company LPP

06/2012 - 12/2014

Printer

Silny & Salamon

Place: Gdynia

Printing graphics and barcodes on plastic seals

LANGUAGES

Polish

Native language

English

C1 (CAE certificate)

German

B1 (still learning)

French

Α1

ACADEMIC ACTIVITY

10/2015 - 06/2016

FILM STUDIES ACTIVITIES AT UNIVERSITY OF GDANSK

Weekly meetings that include discussion about some part of the history of the cinema connected with film shows

01/2015 - 12/2015

AIESEC

Financial analyst – preparation of monthly statements for local committee

HR project – recruiting students for internships abroad

INTERESTS

Web engineering, history of cinema, football, books, technology, cooking, travelling, hitch-hiking, chinese culture, video editing